[Testing London, GB](https://testmy.net/mirror "Test Mirrors") | [Multithread off](https://testmy.net/multithread/?rel=ref "Enable Multithread")   | [Sign In](https://testmy.net/signin) / [Sign Up](https://testmy.net/signup)

[testmy.net  

Internet Speed Test](https://testmy.net/)

### Privacy Policy

TestMy.net respects your privacy and takes a very strong stance against SPAM, Adware and Spyware. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available in our footer and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

Log files are maintained and analyzed of all requests for files on this website's web servers. Log files do not capture personal information but do capture the user's IP address, which is automatically recognized by our web servers.

###### Our Commitment to Children's Privacy

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13 and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

###### Cookies

This website does not store any information that would, on its own, allow us to identify individual users of this service without their permission. Any cookies that may be used by this website are used either solely on a per session basis or to maintain user preferences. Cookies are not shared with any third parties.

###### Any Information Collected is Confidential

**Any and all personal information collected at this site will be kept strictly confidential and will NOT be sold, reused, rented, loaned or otherwise disclosed.** Any information you give to TestMy.net will be held with the utmost care and will not be used in ways that you have not consented to. A more detailed explanation about how we safeguard your personal information is described below. If you have any questions, please don't hesitate to [ask](https://testmy.net/contact).

###### Resale or Disclosure of Information to Third Parties

TestMy.net does not sell, rent, loan, trade or lease any personal information collected at our site, including membership forms or email lists. TestMy.net forums further employ a Private Message system so that members can contact you without having your email address released. Your email address is never visible to the public.

###### Browser Information Collected on the Website

A cookie is a small data file containing certain information and is written to your hard drive when you visit the website. A cookie cannot be read by a website other than the one that sets the cookie. Most cookies last only through a single session or visit.

We use cookies for many reasons here at TestMy.net. All of which are used for the functionality of the our programs. We also use outside Ad agencies to display default (unsold inventory) banners on our site. These ads may contain cookies that are collected by them and we do not have direct access to such information. Please see the "Third Parties" section of this document.

###### Third Parties & Use of Cookies

We also use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit TestMy.net. These companies may use information (NOT including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies visit [Google Privacy](https://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

###### California Consumer Privacy Act (“CCPA”)

Under CCPA, Californian residents have the right to declare their preferences on the sale of data for advertising and marketing purposes. If you wish to change your preferences, click this link to launch our preference portal:

We use a third-party to provide monetisation technologies for our site. You can review their privacy and cookie policy [here](https://publift.com/privacy-policy/).

###### Connection ID & Results Sharing Privacy

You may notice a "Connection ID" in your results. This is a proprietary number used ONLY by TestMy.net and does not correlate with any of your personal information. All the information that is made publicly available about your test results at TestMy.net is safe to share with your friends and the Internet. The only information that is even remotely personal in your results is your username. If you don't want this included we recommend that you signup again and use an ambiguous username.

###### Contact

All correspondence to and from ANY testmy.net address or ANY address directly affiliated with an owner of TestMy Net LLC are subject to public scrutiny at the discretion of [TestMy.net's owner](https://testmy.net/contact) or TestMy Net LLC.

If you have any questions about our policies or ever need clarification please direct them to [TestMy.net's owner](https://testmy.net/contact).

[TestMy.net](https://testmy.net/) © 2024 - [Terms & Privacy](https://testmy.net/legal) - [Contact](https://testmy.net/contact)
